Who invited the freshmen?
Incoming is a comedy film directed by Dave Chernin.
Their first week of high school.
The biggest party of the year.
Mistakes will be made as four teenage boys navigate
a night of mayhem and debauchery.
Benj Nielsen, played by Mason Thames.
Eddie, played by Ramon Reed.
Connor, played by Raphael Alejandro.
Bailey, played by Isabella Ferreira.
Danah 'Koosh' Koushani, played by Bardia Seiri.
Katrina Aurienna, played by Loren Gray.
Incoming is a 2024 American teen comedy film written and directed by Dave
Chernin and John Chernin in their feature length debut.
The film stars Mason Thames and Bobby Cannavale.
The film follows Benj and his friends Eddie, Connor and Koosh as they
navigate their first weeks as high school freshmen.
It was released on Netflix on August 23, 2024.
The film explores themes of high school, coming of age, party, teenager.
The tone is lighthearted.